
var quiz = {
    "JS": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Nguyen Du is considered a famous Vietnamese ............",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "poetry",
                    "b": "poet",
                    "c": "poetic",
                    "d": "poem"
                },
            ],
            "answer": "poet",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "The national dress of Japanese women is .............",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Áo dài",
                    "b": "Sari",
                    "c": "Jeans",
                    "d": "Kimono"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Kimono",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "By learning English, you can get access to the world's ................",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "develop",
                    "b": "development",
                    "c": "developed",
                    "d": "developing"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "development",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Mai often goes to the....... to pray because her religion is Buddism.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "temple",
                    "b": "church",
                    "c": "mosque",
                    "d": "pagoda",
                }
            ],
            "answer": "pagoda",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "The Áo dài is the ........... dress of Vietnamese women.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "casual",
                    "b": "beautiful",
                    "c": "traditional",
                    "d": "baggy",
                }
            ],
            "answer": "traditional",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "I come from Viet Nam so I am not used to ......................... on the left.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "driving",
                    "b": "drive",
                    "c": "drove",
                    "d": "driven"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "driving",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "In Vietnam, it is normally .............. in the South than in the North.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "hot",
                    "b": "hotter",
                    "c": "hottest",
                    "d": "hoter"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "hotter",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Ho Chi Minh city is ................... than Hanoi.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "smaller",
                    "b": "bigger",
                    "c": "biggest",
                    "d": "smallest"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "bigger",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Vietnamese people are very .....................",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "friend",
                    "b": "friendly",
                    "c": "friendship",
                    "d": "friendliness"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "friendly",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "............... are written to make people laugh.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Tragedies",
                    "b": "Novels",
                    "c": "Funny stories",
                    "d": "Fictions"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Funny stories",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "If you study at College, you can live in a ……….. on campus.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "hotel",
                    "b": "mobile room",
                    "c": "private room",
                    "d": "dormitory"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "dormitory",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "The Internet is available in our city, so we can ............... get access to it.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "easily",
                    "b": "easy",
                    "c": "uneasily",
                    "d": "uneasy"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "easily",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "Mathematics and Literature are ............. subjects in high schools.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "optional",
                    "b": "adding",
                    "c": "religious",
                    "d": "compulsory"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "compulsory",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "We can protect the environment by ................. air pollution.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "reusing",
                    "b": "reuse",
                    "c": "reducing",
                    "d": "reduce"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "reducing",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "…….. is one of the six socio-political organisations in Viet Nam?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union",
                    "b": "Communist Party of Viet Nam",
                    "c": "The People's Courts of the Socialist Republic of Vietnam",
                    "d": "The National Assembly of the Socialist Republic of Vietnam"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "……….. is a member of the World Federation of Trade Unions?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Viet Nam General Federation of Labour",
                    "b": "Viet Nam General Confederation of Labour",
                    "c": "Viet Nam Youth Federation",
                    "d": "Viet Nam Fatherland Front"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Viet Nam General Confederation of Labour",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "I am a Ho Chi Minh Communist ………………",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Student",
                    "b": "Young people",
                    "c": "Youth Union Cadre",
                    "d": "Youth"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Youth Union Cadre",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "Fast food is very popular …………….., a diet of hamburgers, pizzas and fried chicken is not very healthy.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Consequently",
                    "b": "Moreover",
                    "c": "Unfortunately",
                    "d": "In contrast"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Unfortunately",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "According to Article 1 of the …………… Law 2020, young people who are Vietnamese citizens from full 16 to 30 years old.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Young people",
                    "b": "Young generation",
                    "c": "Young",
                    "d": "Youth"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Youth",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "He always studies the ……………. in the paper as he wants to find a good second-hand car.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "advertisements",
                    "b": "publicity",
                    "c": "announcements",
                    "d": "publication"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "advertisements",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "In which of the following cases is the employment contract automatically terminated?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "The employee is on maternity leave",
                    "b": "The employee is detained or detained",
                    "c": "The employee is doing military service",
                    "d": "The employee is sentenced to prison"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "The employee is sentenced to prison",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "question": "According to the Labor Law, children from 13 years old to under 15 years old can work no more than how many hours a day?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Two hour",
                    "b": "Four hour",
                    "c": "Six hour",
                    "d": "Eight hour"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Four hour",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "question": "What are the criteria for considering the title \"Student with 3 Good Training Criteria\" in Ho Chi Minh City?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Good morals - Good study - Good physical strength",
                    "b": "Good morals - Good foreign languages - Good physical strength",
                    "c": "Practice morality and manner - Practice skills - Practice skills and physical strength",
                    "d": "Practice morality - Practice skills - Practice physical strength"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Good morals - Good study - Good physical strength",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "question": "How many levels does the organizational system of the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union have?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "3 levels",
                    "b": "5 levels",
                    "c": "9 levels",
                    "d": "4 levels"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "4 levels",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "question": "Who was the First Secretary of the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union Central Committee in Vietnam?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Comrades Nguyễn Văn Cừ",
                    "b": "Comrades Nguyễn Lam",
                    "c": "Comrades Trần Bạch Đằng",
                    "d": "Comrades Hoàng Phương"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Comrades Nguyễn Văn Cừ",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "question": "Who is the author of the current badge of the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Artist Nguyễn Văn Thuận",
                    "b": "Artist Nguyễn Gia Trí",
                    "c": "Artist Tô Ngọc Vân",
                    "d": "Artist Bùi Xuân Phái"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Artist Tô Ngọc Vân",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "question": "The Saigon River does not pass through which districts of Ho Chi Minh City?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Củ Chi District",
                    "b": "Hóc Môn District",
                    "c": "Nhà Bè District",
                    "d": "Bình Chánh District"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Bình Chánh District",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "question": "What is the form of personnel election at all levels in the organization of the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Negotiate",
                    "b": "Vote",
                    "c": "Secret ballot",
                    "d": "Recommend"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Secret ballot",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "question": "What is the first national name of our country?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Đại Cồ Việt",
                    "b": "Đại Việt",
                    "c": "Đại Nam",
                    "d": "Văn Lang"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Văn Lang",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "question": "\"The path of youth is only the path of revolution, there can be no other path\". Whose statement was that?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Comrades Lý Tự Trọng",
                    "b": "Comrades Trần Phú",
                    "c": "Comrades Trần Văn Ơn",
                    "d": "Comrades Nguyễn Văn Linh"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Comrades Trần Phú",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "question": "The Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union organizes and operates on which principle?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Cooperation, equality, coordination, and unified action",
                    "b": "Democratic consultations",
                    "c": "Democratic centralization",
                    "d": "Voluntary, self-management."
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Democratic centralization",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "question": "In the case of the death of an employee participating in voluntary social insurance, will the person taking care of the funeral receive funeral benefits?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Social insurance payment period is 30 months or more",
                    "b": "Social insurance payment period is 40 months or more",
                    "c": "Social insurance payment period is 50 months or more",
                    "d": "Social insurance payment period is 60 months or more"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Social insurance payment period is 60 months or more",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "question": "Who is the current President of the Socialist Republic of Vietnam?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Comrades Nguyễn Phú Trọng",
                    "b": "Comrades Vương Đình Huệ",
                    "c": "Comrades Võ Văn Thưởng",
                    "d": "Comrades Nguyễn Xuân Phúc"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Comrades Nguyễn Xuân Phúc",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "question": "What is the severance pay for employees who work regularly for 12 months or more when the labor contract is terminated?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Each year of work is subsidized with ½ month of the regional minimum wage",
                    "b": "Each year of work is subsidized with ½ month's salary on total income",
                    "c": "Each year of work is subsidized with ½ month's salary",
                    "d": "Unsubsidized"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Each year of work is subsidized with ½ month's salary",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 35,
            "question": "If you would like to confirm your___in the course, please call us at the number listed on the front page.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "replacement",
                    "b": "appointment",
                    "c": "enrollment",
                    "d": "recruitment"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "enrollment",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 36,
            "question": "\"We will not leave until we see the manager,\" said the customers.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "The customers promised to leave before they saw the manager.",
                    "b": "The customers refused to leave until they saw the manager.",
                    "c": "The customers agreed to leave before they saw the manager.",
                    "d": "The customers decided to leave because they did not see the manager."
                }
            ],
            "answer": "The customers refused to leave until they saw the manager.",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 37,
            "question": "He was successful because he was determined to pursue personal goals. He was not talented.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "It was his determination to pursue personal goals, not talent, that contributed to his success.",
                    "b": "In addition to his determination, his talent ensured his success in pursing his goals.",
                    "c": "His success lay in his natural ability, not his determination to pursue personal goals.",
                    "d": "His determination to pursue personal goals made him successful and talented."
                }
            ],
            "answer": "It was his determination to pursue personal goals, not talent, that contributed to his success.",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 38,
            "question": "Please indicate the highest leadership agency of the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "National Congress of Youth Union delegates",
                    "b": "Youth Union Executive Committees at all levels",
                    "c": "Congress of Youth Union delegates at all levels.",
                    "d": "Standing Committee of Youth Union at all levels"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "National Congress of Youth Union delegates",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 39,
            "question": "Charter of Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union issued by?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "The Central Youth Union Secretariat voted to approve",
                    "b": "The Central Executive Committee meeting voted to approve",
                    "c": "The National Delegates Congress voted to approve",
                    "d": "The Standing Committee of the Central Youth Union voted to approve"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "The National Delegates Congress voted to approve",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "question": "Which art has been honored by UNESCO as a representative intangible cultural heritage of humanity in Ho Chi Minh City in particular and the Southern region in general?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Hát bội miền Nam",
                    "b": "Dạ cổ hoài lang",
                    "c": "Đờn ca tài tử Nam Bộ",
                    "d": "Nghệ thuật Xòe Thái"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Đờn ca tài tử Nam Bộ",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 41,
            "question": "Who founded the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Founded by the Communist Party of Vietnam"
                    ,
                    "b": "Founded by President Ho Chi Minh"
                    ,
                    "c": "Founded by the Communist Party of Vietnam and President Ho Chi Minh"
                    ,
                    "d": "Founded by the predecessor of the Communist Party of Vietnam"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Founded by the Communist Party of Vietnam and President Ho Chi Minh",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 42,
            "question": "Who determines the tasks and powers of the National Committee on Youth of Viet Nam?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Prime Minister"
                    ,
                    "b": "Government"
                    ,
                    "c": "Ministry of Home Affairs"
                    ,
                    "d": "The National Assembly"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Prime Minister",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 43,
            "question": "Young people are Vietnamese citizens ................................. .",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "from 14 years old to 30 years old."
                    ,
                    "b": "from 156 years old to 30 years old."
                    ,
                    "c": "from 16 years old to 30 years old."
                    ,
                    "d": "from 18 years old to 30 years old."
                }
            ],
            "answer": "from 16 years old to 30 years old.",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 44,
            "question": "The Youth Law 2020 regulates the role of youth in Article 4 on the roles, rights and obligations of youth as follows:",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Youth are a great social force, pioneering, creative, and at the forefront of innovation, building and protecting the socialist Vietnamese Homeland; plays an important role in the cause of industrialization, modernization of the country, international integration and building socialism."
                    ,
                    "b": "Youth are a great social force, pioneering, creative, and at the forefront of innovation, building and protecting the socialist Vietnamese Homeland; plays a particularly important rolea particularly important role in the cause of industrialization, modernization of the country, international integration and building socialism."
                    ,
                    "c": "Youth are a great social force, pioneering, creative, and at the forefront of innovation, building and protecting the socialist Vietnamese Homeland; plays a particularly important rolea particularly important role in the cause of modernization of the country, international integration and building socialism.."
                    ,
                    "d": "Youth are a great social force, pioneering, creative, and at the forefront of innovation, building and protecting the socialist Vietnamese Homeland; plays a particularly important rolea particularly important role in the cause of modernization of the country and building socialism."
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Youth are a great social force, pioneering, creative, and at the forefront of innovation, building and protecting the socialist Vietnamese Homeland; plays an important role in the cause of industrialization, modernization of the country, international integration and building socialism.",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 45,
            "question": "What are the minimum conditions to establish a Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth chapter?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "There are at least 5 Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth members."
                    ,
                    "b": "There are at least 3 Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth members."
                    ,
                    "c": "There are at least 10 Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth members."
                    ,
                    "d": "Just need to have Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth members (number doesn't matter)."
                }
            ],
            "answer": "There are at least 3 Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth members.",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 46,
            "question": "The Youth Union's Charter stipulates that youth of what age can be admitted to the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "From 15 years old to 30 years old"
                    ,
                    "b": "From 15 years old to 30 years old"
                    ,
                    "c": "From 16 years old to 30 years old"
                    ,
                    "d": "From 14 years old to 30 years old"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "From 16 years old to 30 years old",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 47,
            "question": "Which of the following contracts can be concluded verbally?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "For temporary jobs with a term of from 3 months to less than 6 months"
                    ,
                    "b": "For temporary jobs with a term of less than 12 months"
                    ,
                    "c": "For temporary jobs with a term of less than 3 months"
                    ,
                    "d": "For temporary jobs with a term of less than 9 months"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "For temporary jobs with a term of less than 3 months",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 48,
            "question": "Action slogan of the City's youth at the 11th Congress of the Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union in Ho Chi Minh City?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "Aspiration - Pioneering - Solidarity - Bravery - Creativity"
                    ,
                    "b": "Patriotism - Solidarity - Pioneering - Creativity - Integration"
                    ,
                    "c": "Pioneering - Solidarity - Bravery - Creativity"
                    ,
                    "d": "Solidarity - Impulse - Bravery - Creativity"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "Patriotism - Solidarity - Pioneering - Creativity - Integration",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 49,
            "question": "Stephan Roach projected that the global economy, which ....... in the first quarter of this year at a 5 percent growth, will slow down over the course of the year.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "reached"
                    ,
                    "b": "enlarged"
                    ,
                    "c": "maximized"
                    ,
                    "d": "peaked"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "peaked",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        },
        {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "Buyers have no legal ……....... to disclose their personal financial information to anyone.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "a": "management"
                    ,
                    "b": "promise"
                    ,
                    "c": "engagement"
                    ,
                    "d": "obligation"
                }
            ],
            "answer": "obligation",
            "score": 0,
            "status": ""
        }
    ]
}
var quizApp = function () {
    this.score = 0;
    this.qno = 1;
    this.currentque = 0;
    var totalque = quiz.JS.length;
    this.displayQuiz = function (cque) {
        this.currentque = cque;
        if (this.currentque < totalque) {
            $("#tque").html(totalque);
            $("#previous").attr("disabled", false);
            $("#next").attr("disabled", false);
            $("#qid").html(quiz.JS[this.currentque].id + '.');
            $("#question").html(quiz.JS[this.currentque].question);
            $("#question-options").html("");
            for (var key in quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0]) {
                if (quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0].hasOwnProperty(key)) {
                    $("#question-options").append(
                        "<div class='form-check option-block'>" +
                        "<label class='form-check-label'>" +
                        "<input type='radio' class='form-check-input' name='option' id='q" + key + "' value='" + quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0][key] + "'><span id='optionval'>" +
                        quiz.JS[this.currentque].options[0][key] +
                        "</span></label>"
                    );
                }
            }
        }
        if (this.currentque <= 0) {
            $("#previous").attr("disabled", true);
        }
        if (this.currentque >= totalque) {
            $('#next').attr('disabled', true);
            for (var i = 0; i < totalque; i++) {
                this.score = this.score + quiz.JS[i].score;
            }
            return this.showResult(this.score);
        }

    }
    this.showResult = function (scr) {
        $("#result").addClass('result');
        $("#result").html("<h1 class='res-header'>Total Score: &nbsp;" + scr + '/' + totalque + "</h1>");
        for (var j = 0; j < totalque; j++) {
            var res;
            if (quiz.JS[j].score == 0) {
                res = '<span class="wrong">' + quiz.JS[j].score + '</span><i class="fa fa-remove c-wrong"></i>';
            } else {
                res = '<span class="correct">' + quiz.JS[j].score + '</span><i class="fa fa-check c-correct"></i>';
            }
            $("#result").append(
                '<div class="result-question"><span>Q ' + quiz.JS[j].id + '</span> &nbsp;' + quiz.JS[j].question + '</div>' +
                '<div><b>Correct answer:</b> &nbsp;' + quiz.JS[j].answer + '</div>' +
                '<div class="last-row"><b>Score:</b> &nbsp;' + res +
                '</div>'
            );
        }
    }
    this.checkAnswer = function (option) {
        var answer = quiz.JS[this.currentque].answer;
        option = option.replace(/</g, "&lt;") //for <
        option = option.replace(/>/g, "&gt;") //for >
        option = option.replace(/"/g, "&quot;")
        if (option == quiz.JS[this.currentque].answer) {
            if (quiz.JS[this.currentque].score == "") {
                quiz.JS[this.currentque].score = 1;
                quiz.JS[this.currentque].status = "correct";
            }
        } else {
            quiz.JS[this.currentque].status = "wrong";
        }
    }
    this.changeQuestion = function (cque) {
        this.currentque = this.currentque + cque;
        this.displayQuiz(this.currentque);
    }
}
var jsq = new quizApp();
var selectedopt;
$(document).ready(function () {
    jsq.displayQuiz(0);
    $('#question-options').on('change', 'input[type=radio][name=option]', function (e) {
        //var radio = $(this).find('input:radio');
        $(this).prop("checked", true);
        selectedopt = $(this).val();
    });
});
$("#submit").click(function () {
    $('#next').attr('disabled', true);
    for (var i = 0; i < quiz.JS.length; i++) {
        jsq.score = jsq.score + quiz.JS[i].score;
    }
    return jsq.showResult(jsq.score);
})
$('#next').click(function (e) {
    e.preventDefault();
    if (selectedopt) {
        jsq.checkAnswer(selectedopt);
    }
    jsq.changeQuestion(1);
});
$('#previous').click(function (e) {
    e.preventDefault();
    if (selectedopt) {
        jsq.checkAnswer(selectedopt);
    }
    jsq.changeQuestion(-1);
});
